okay the time is up
Welcome everyone to the AI plus industry meeting
hosted by the Yisichangtian team
I am your host tonight: AFAN. In our previous sessions
we've already had discussions with students from fields
such as Environmental Science, Metallurgy
Agriculture, Materials Science
Finance, 3D Printing
Integrated Circuits and Brain Science
We've gained a lot of industry related knowledge
for those interested
You can watch the replays on our bilibili account
Today's live stream will also be edited
and uploaded to bilibili
Today we are pleased to have invited Ali
a doctoral candidate
at Shenzhen Institutes of advanced technology
Chinese Academy of Sciences
to talk about his perspective on the application of AI
in the health care sector
Ali's researchs focus on microwave
imaging from breast cancer detection and localization
as well as the application of large language models in health care
during the presentation
you can ask questions and engage in discussion in the chat area